纳达尔队 4-3 穆雷队 · 赛后捧杯致辞
Well, thank you for the words.
谢谢你刚才说的这些话
First of all, yeah,
首先
next time we can play golf,
下次我们可以打高尔夫
maybe you have a better chance.
也许你赢的机会会大些
So I know you are practicing
我知道你平时练习
a lot more than me.
比我多得多
So maybe
所以 也许
the next Rafa Nadal Academy Slam
下一届纳达尔学院Slam
can be in golf.
可以改打高尔夫
So let's try.
我们试试看吧
But anyway, thank you very much,
不过 无论如何 非常感谢
Fabio, Marat, Dominic, Andy,
弗格尼尼 萨芬 蒂姆 穆雷
Carlos, David, Richard,
莫亚 费雷尔 加斯奎特
for me personally.
对我个人来说
And I think for everybody here
我想 对这里每一个人来说
in my village, Manacor,
在我的家乡马纳科尔
and the island of Mallorca.
以及整个马略卡岛
And of course, for all the kids
当然 也包括所有孩子
and workers, have been amazing
和工作人员 能与大家一起
to share this very special moment
分享这个特别的时刻
with all of you.
真的太美好了
So thank you for being part
谢谢大家一起度过
of this unforgettable day.
这个难忘的日子
Thank you so much.
非常感谢
Bueno, quiero dar las gracias
我想感谢
también a todos.
所有人
Vull donar ses gràcies a tots.
我要感谢所有人
els que [unclear] heu acompanyat
感谢今天陪伴我的人
en el dia d'avui.
一起度过今天
I want to thank everybody
现场英语 我要感谢大家
that came out today.
感谢今天到场的每一个人
[Applause and indistinct voices]
掌声 夹杂未辨识人声
Com sabeu, aquest lloc és
大家知道 这里
un lloc molt especial per a jo,
对我而言是特别的地方
i realment veure [unclear] que
看到大家的支持
rebem aquí a Manacor,
在马纳科尔
i a Mallorca, en general,
在整个马略卡岛
per això és una gran satisfacció,
这让我十分欣慰
Només puc donar les gràcies
我只能向大家致谢
per haver volgut la part d'aquest dia,
谢谢你们愿意参与今天
que jo crec que serà inolvidable per
我相信 这将是难忘的一天
aquesta acadèmia.
对这所学院而言
Se van complint etapes i avui
我们走过一个又一个阶段
és un dia de celebració. Deu anys
今天是庆祝的日子 十年
és un número realment important,
是一个很重要的数字
per a nosaltres, pensant com van
对我们来说 回想最初
començar i pensant on som avui,
如何开始 再看今天的我们
realment sense l'ajuda de l'altre
如果没有大家的帮助
i de tota aquesta gent
没有这些人
que s'està esforçant dia
日复一日的努力
a dia per fer d'aquest lloc,
努力让这个地方
un lloc especial que
成为一个特别的地方
rebem gent de tot el món,
汇聚世界各地的人们
seria impossible. Moltíssimes
这不可能做到 非常感谢
gràcies per tot el vostre suport.
感谢大家的支持
Speaking in their local dialects,
转播评论 他用当地语言
thanking everybody for a special day
感谢大家共同度过这一天
for him and 10 years.
这个特别的十周年日子
It's something very, very special.
转播评论 这意义非凡
Thank you for being a part of it.
转播译述 感谢大家参与
And I will remember this day forever.
转播译述 永远记住今天
Para terminar, quiero agradecer
最后 我要感谢
a todos los medios que nos habéis
所有媒体 感谢你们
acompañado en este día.
今天陪伴我们
Gracias por darnos la cobertura en
谢谢你们报道
este bonito día.
这个美好的日子
Y por último, antes de despedirme,
最后 在告别之前
quiero dar las gracias a un muy buen
我要感谢一位很好的
amigo y uno de los mejores artistas
朋友 也是顶尖艺人之一
de nuestro país de las últimas
我国近几十年来
décadas como es David Bisbal.
他就是大卫 比斯巴尔
Gracias por haber querido
谢谢你愿意来
acompañarnos.
陪伴我们
Hace que el cierre de esta fiesta
让这场庆典的收尾
pues sea muy bonito,
变得这么美好
sea que a mí personalmente me
对我个人而言
hace mucha ilusión que estés aquí
你能来到这里 我特别高兴
con nosotros David y seguro que
大卫 我相信
a toda la gente de aquí de Mallorca
马略卡的所有人
de Manacor también.
马纳科尔的大家也一样
O sea, muchísimas gracias por todo,
所以 非常感谢你的一切
y gracias.
谢谢
I'm very proud that you are here
转播译述 你在此我很自豪
with us and before the closing ceremony.
转播译述 闭幕前和我们相聚